♫ In the not-too-distant future
♫ Next Sunday, A.D.
♫ There was a guy named Joel
♫ Not too different from you or me
♫ He worked in a Gizmonic Institute
♫ Just another face in a red jumpsuit
♫ He did a good job cleaning up the place
♫ But his bosses didn't like him
♫ So they shot him into space
♫ We'll send him cheesy movies
♫ The worst we can find la-la-la
♫ He'll have to sit and watch them all
♫ And we'll monitor his mind la-la-la
♫ Now keep in mind Joel can't control
♫ When the movies begin or end la-la-la
♫ Because he used those special parts
♫ To make his robot friends
♫ Robot roll call
♫ Cambot
♫ Gypsy
♫ Tom Servo
♫ Crow
♫ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♫ And other science facts la la la
♫ Then repeat to yourself it's just a show
♫ I should really just relax
♫ For Mystery Science Theater 3000
(doors closing)
- Yes
(laughing)
- Okay Tommer, looks
like he's ready to roll,
why don't you go get Joel?
- Okie.
Hey Joel!
- Criminy Servo!
I could've done that.
- Hi one and all, welcome
to the satellite of love.
Hey fellas, what up?
- Oh we only built the most sophisticated
robotistical invention ever!
- Yeah, his name is Minsky.
Now just push that button on
the top Joel, to fire him up.
- Alright.
(quirky beeping)
- Get this, get this, get this.
Here it comes.
- I am the Atomic Alan Robot!
Please give my best wishes to everybody!
- Oh that's nice.
I imagine it's just one of the
really neat things he does.
- Oh, what do you mean?
- I am the Atomic Alan Robot!
Please give my best wishes to everybody!
- Oh I get it, you installed
that annoying phrase
to balance out the truly
cool things he does, right?
- No, it just does the friendly voice.
- Yeah, we thought it kind
of distills our own lives
quite well.
- Wait, here it comes again!
- Yeah.
- I am the atomic Alan robot!
Please give my best wishes to everybody.
- [Voiceover] 15 seconds
to commercial sign,
and keep that thing out of my hair!
- Okay.
- I am the atomic Alan robot!
Please give my best wishes to everybody!
- Guys, do you think we
could turn that off now?
I'm kind of getting a headache.
- Nope, he's a new form of life
and he doesn't have an off switch.
- It's yours now, Joel.
To steward, to nurture.
- I love doing good things for people.
- Oh, me too.
- We'll be right back.
- He has your eyes.
- He has your head.
- Oh he does!
Nice pooper on him, too.
(happy music)
(thuds)
- So I think he was just,
how are you two getting along in here?
Hey!
- Nothing! Noth--
- Oh, you were too!
- Nancy and Sluggo are
calling on the phone.
- Oh, hi Joel.
That was really something.
Eheheh.
Well anyway, Dr. Forrester's
been away since last Tuesday.
I finally convinced him to go
to one of his class reunions.
He's got nothing to be ashamed of.
So I've taken it upon myself to develop
this week's invention exchange.
Now, we've all heard of
virtual reality right?
The gloves, the goggles, the wires?
Well I've come up with a
similar concept that allows
the average person to
achieve that universal goal,
becoming a stand-up comedian.
It actually puts you inside
the total comedy club
environment with the laughter,
the clinking glasses,
the waitresses, the overpriced drinks.
It's something I like
to call virtual comedy
and I think it just might go
a little something like this.
(audience laughing)
Oh thank you, thank you, thank you.
You guys are a great crowd thank
you for coming out tonight.
Well, what can I tell you about myself?
Well, I'm single.
(laughs)
Big surprise there, huh?
(laughing)
(audience applauding)
Oh thanks, you guys are great.
Give yourselves a round
of applause for coming out
and supporting live comedy.
- All this adulation can't
be too good for Frank,
let's see how he deals with
a couple of drunken hecklers.
- Oh what else?
Oh I well went to visit my mother.
That's always a good thing to do.
On the way there, I got
pulled over by some cops--
- [Voiceover] You suck.
- God I hate.
Huh?
- [Voiceover] You're not funny!
- Well you're...
pretty ugly, is what you are.
(audience jeering)
Well I'm sorry, I didn't mean to imply.
- It's almost too easy.
Your turn, Joel.
- I tell ya what,
I'm gonna bring out your
headliner right now.
- Well sirs, we've all played
miniature golf into the
small hours and it presents
quite a few nagging questions.
- Like is it really golf?
- No, it's not.
- And is it really miniature?
- Oh not at all, it takes
up a heck of a lot of space.
- Hence this week's invention.
- Not only have we taken golf
and turned it truly microscopic.
- [Crow] Witness the microscope.
- But microgolf really is actual golf.
Here's how it works.
On each of these slides
is an entire golf course.
Combining the technical
know-how of biologists like
Alexander Fleming, with the
impeccable course design
acumen of Jack Nicklaus,
and Chai Trirodiguys
- Each course is
constructed of lush E. Coli,
partimen specimen, and the
finest subcutaneous basha.
- Okay, now I use this paramecium
for a seven iron right?
- Right Joel, but I'd
consider the euglena niblick
on this shot, and try
to put some spin on it.
- In keeping with the
grandeur of micro golf,
let us speak In hushed tones.
- Alright, and uh!
- Robinson teed off moments ago on the
short par five eleventh, normally
considered a birdie hole.
He really let fly using a
medium-shafted mitochondria,
his Golgi body sitting a neat
.07 micromillimeters from the flag.
- Robinson really needs a birdie
because the wheels have been coming off.
- This shot is a bit
trickier than it looks,
what with the lymphatic
plasma to the left,
and the green sloping
towards the nucleoli.
- Alright I'm lining the
pernicious anemia culture,
I'm gonna use my pitching
wedge to loft it.
- Oh, the wheels really are coming off.
- There they go!
- Whaddya think, sirs?
- All in all I'm glad I went, Frank.
I think I came off rather well.
- I didn't mean anything by that.
Actually your wife is very lovely, sir.
No, please sit down, it
was all in good humor.
You're a really nice audience.
(audience jeering)
- Frank really does stink, you know?
Anyway Joel, your experiment
this week has a dual purpose.
Oh, it'll hurt like always,
but my little trip to the
Alma mater reminded me that I
had done some undergrad study
in the field of supervillanry.
I'll be conducting a little seminar after
the film, taking some questions.
In the meantime, please enjoy
Secret Agent Superdragon.
- Security, security!
No, no, no.
- Shh!
- Joel's teeing off!
- .004!
(alarm sounding)
Ah, we got movie sign!
(doors opening)
Hey looks kind of like a
Micky Spaleen still-life.
- [Crow] Oh it's called Secret Agent-
Hey!
(mysterious jazz music)
- [Tom] Dig the tunes.
- [Joel] One of these things
is not like the other,
one of these things just.
- [Crow] Someone left a
crayon burning, I hate that!
- [Joel] By special arrangement?
What, did they have to get
her out of the fourth grade?
- [Tom] Sir, you have
a call on chamber four.
(humming)
- [Crow] And of course,
technicolor as himself.
- [Joel] (coughs) You know
I'm gonna sue this movie
for secondhand smoke.
- [Tom] Suggested by?
"Hey why don't you guys write a screenplay
"but give me credit for it okay?"
- [Crow] Boy I bet the hero
of this film is really cool.
He smokes, he carries a gun
and he makes a lot of phone calls.
- [Joel] Brought to you by Firestone!
- [Tom] Where the rubber meets the road.
(buzzing)
- [Tom] Oh, J. Edgar Hoo Hoo Hoover.
- [Crow] Secret Agent Mary Kay!
(mysterious music)
- [Joel] Oh man, she doesn't
have any blushers, forget it.
- [Tom] Oh damn these things,
which key is it I can never remember.
Too many, I have to get
rid of a couple of these.
(mimicking alarms beeping)
(mimics dog barking)
Oh, watch this.
They're gonna pan up, and
it's gonna be John Cleese.
Say.
- [Joel] You know eventually
this is gonna get annoying.
- Eventually?
- [Tom] Oh no, it's a Hercules film!
I hope that's not the secret
agent dragon man there.
- [Crow] Hey who pulled
William Holden out of the pool?
- [Tom] That they did.
- [Joel] Oh you can tell by
the lawn furniture that
he's a secret agent.
- [Tom] Oh no, she's gonna open letters!
- [Crow] We now return to I, Claudius.
- [Joel] Oh that's more
pink than I would ever wear.
- [Tom] Well, he's done on that side.
- [Joel] Hey, look how far
you can see into his nose.
- [Crow] Secret Agent Super Booger.
- [Tom] Pepper, you're going undercover!
(ticking)
- [Crow] Oh no, Madame Sousatzka was here!
- [Joel] Hey I hope she's
speeding up the film.
- [Tom] Ladies and
gentlemen, Joey Heatherton!
(mimicking erotic jazz music)
- [Crow] What is this, a Bergman film?
- [Tom] It's 10:30, do you
know where your hot chick is?
- [Joel] Oh, I gotta remember
to write that dream down!
- [Crow] Wait a minute, I'm Scott Baio!
- [Tom] Oh, buffalo
shot, sorry about that.
- Comfort, how'd you
ever find me here, huh?
- Do your horrible yoga
exercises permit you to kiss me?
- Oh not exactly.
This is for comfort.
And this.
- [Joel] Is for grandma.
- [Comfort] Let me go, Bryan! (screams)
- [Crow] Boy, relationships
with secretaries
were a lot different back then.
- [Crow] Already I'm a dickweed.
- [Joel] Hey got any gum?
- That's a nice way to here.
Come on, pull me out of here you big oaf!
I'm not agent Fulton, I'm not on duty.
(crow yelping)
- The boss sent you, didn't he?
- No, Coleman didn't
send me, it was my idea.
I thought you'd be pleased to see me,
but I see I was wrong.
- C'mon tell me, why did you come, really.
- [Crow] I thought you were Matt Helm.
- Alright.
Coleman did send me out on assignment.
We need Super Dragon.
- Oh no no no.
Super Dragon no longer exists.
- [Joel] Oh, no, no, no.
- I'm just plain Bryan Cooper, now.
But I'm listening.
Go ahead.
- Have you ever heard
of Fremont, Michigan?
- [Bryan] Yeah, it's a little
college town, isn't it?
- That's right.
Just an ordinary college town,
til strange things started to happen.
- [Bryan] Like what?
- Two healthy students
suddenly die of heart failure.
- [Tom] Oh I've heard this one.
- Four others strangely collapse from
an unknown nervous disorder.
Fights break out for no
reason, and no one can explain
how all this insanity has
overtaken the whole student body.
- [Crow] It's college, lighten up.
- The local doctors and police
don't have any connection.
But Coleman smells something burning.
- [Joel] Well they makes stoves.
- And you want me to put out the fire,
well not on your life,
I've got my firemen's suit
hanging up in the closet there.
- You could cancel your resignation.
- Not on your life.
- [Tom] He has no batch!
He's perfectly smooth!
- [Crow] Really?
- That's the story, except
for agent Wilson who was
sent to investigate.
He was found dead after four days at the
bottom of an elevator shaft.
(scatting Shaft theme)
- He worked with me for ten years.
If anything's wrong in Fremont,
he should be able to handle it.
Don't you worry about it.
No no no, you let me handle this.
Even Coleman hasn't got the right
to interrupt a man's privacy.
- [Crow] Oh, that's my Super Dragon.
- [Tom] Fred Winston, WLS Chicago.
- Hello?
- [Voiceover] Oh Cooper?
- Yes it's me, Bryan Cooper talking.
How are you, I'm fine, never felt better!
- [Voiceover] Agent Fulton there?
- That's right, agent Fulton's right here.
But it won't do you any good,
I'm not leaving the place.
- [Caller] Jackson's dead.
- What?
- His car plunged into the river
and he was killed instantly.
Two or three miles outside of Fremont.
- [Joel] How are you?
- We're not convinced it was an accident.
- [Crow] If Fritz Hollings
were supermarionation.
- You were very good friends
and so I wanted to tell you right away.
- Coleman?
Coleman, are you there?
- [Tom] Hello Mr. Coleman,
I seem cut off from you,
hello, hello?
- [Joel] Why he hung up on
me, that son of a. (chuckles)
- [Crow] I'm gonna go lay on
the lawn again, this place.
- Did you hear about Jackson?
- What happened to him?
- He's dead.
- [Tom] Jim.
- You better get dressed.
- [Crow] Bert Convy, PI.
- I'm going to Fremont.
- Your friend's death was an accident.
The trouble is, if one
doesn't know that canyon road,
it can pretty dangerous.
- But Jackson was a very good driver.
- Sure, but folks saw him
pick up a good looking girl.
- [Joel] Oh look, they're in
America cause there's a flag.
- My guess he took his eyes
off the road for an instant.
Those things can happen.
- Who was the girl?
- Christine Brueder,
a girl from Amsterdam.
She's a friend of Mr. Ross, who owns
the bowling alley on Marlboro street.
- [Tom] Oh, where the flavor is.
- But her body wasn't found.
- That's a little
strange, don't you think?
- [Officer] Not at all, it was
probably washed downstream.
- [Crow] Wonder if he's smooth too.
- That's a brilliant explanation.
- This is everything Jackson had with him.
- [Joel] Personal effects make me happy.
- [Officer] These are the
keys to his apartment.
I know my job, eh?
- I hope you're saving your money.
- [Tom] Well, sure,
I've got a six month CD
and an IR, hey.
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] Do, do, do, do.
Hi, honey, I'm smooth.
- [Tom] Ethel?
Yes. (mumbling)
Yes.
- [Crow] Oh, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar.
- [Tom] Hm.
Wait a minute I broke into my own place.
- [Joel] Well that's a weird switch.
- [Crow] Light doesn't
travel as fast in his world.
- [Tom] Now it's time for my kooky slides.
- [Crow] Hm?
- [Joel] Oh, this is before
they had Post-It notes.
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Tom] This is gonna be
even more private than I thought.
Heh, heh, heh.
He's got DNA up on the wall.
It's time for the Banana Split Show.
(cuckoo clock calling)
- [Crow] I'm cuckoo for Coco Puffs.
Cuckoo for Coco Puffs, woo hoo.
- [Tom] I wanna beer back.
Oh wait man, this is
like Pee Wee's Playhouse.
- [Crow] Congratulations on your purchase
of a black forest cuckoo clock.
(happy music)
- [Tom] Hm.
Ross Perot, the early years.
- Ross.
- [Tom] It is Ross.
I hope you're not in
any hurry to close up.
I'd like to have a few words with you.
- What do you want?
- [Tom] I want a Snickers now.
- There's only $10 in the cash drawer.
- I don't want any money, I'll settle for
a lot less than that.
Just some of this gum and
not this stuff either,
but the stuff you give to kids.
Stay there.
'Atta boy.
- [Crow] But I've got a
Charlie Callas audition to,
uh, uh, go to.
- What's um,
what's so special about this?
- Nothin'.
It's just a different brand, that's all.
- [Tom] You're working
for the Wrigley company,
aren't you?
- Now let's talk some more.
What do you know about Christine Brueder?
- [Crow] She chews Juicyfruit, okay?
What do you want from me?
- I don't know anything.
She came here from
Amsterdam about a year ago
and now she's--
- And now she's dead.
- Yes.
- [Tom] Yes, yes.
- Do you believe that?
- [Joel] Um, no?
- Why not?
- [Joel] Uh, yes!
- I don't believe that either.
- [Tom] Don't hit my sore
ear again, Mr. Gowa, please.
- Would you like a stick of chewing gum?
- No, please.
- Come on, take it.
- [Ross] No, no, no.
- [Joel] No, I've got dental work.
- Chew it, chew it.
- [Crow] It's funny joke garlic gum.
- All right, I'll tell you about her.
- All right.
Let's see what you have to say, huh.
- She came from Amsterdam.
I met her.
(gun shots)
(fires gun)
- [Tom] It was P.K. Wrigley himself.
- [Crow] A drive by snack bar assault.
- [Joel] I think you should
talk to your delivery man.
- [Tom] Twin Peaks.
Slapped him a little too hard.
- [Crow] Oh.
The delicious fruit flavor
burst right through his skull.
- [Joel] Tonight,
who wants gum?
- [Tom] He did, he did.
Dun dun ding ding dun dun dun dun.
Hm?
- [Joel] The thin blue lines.
- [Crow] Right above the massage parlor.
- [Tom] That's convenient.
Oh, I get it.
He's an undercover agent
for the apartment guy.
- [Joel] Ah, get that
wind ensemble out of here.
- [Crow] Oh, hello.
Nice but not my color.
Have you got it in salmon pink?
Mm, hm.
- [Tom] Well, what do ya',
super neat, he's got a puppet stage
right here in his room.
- [Joel] Mm, this place is nook crazy,
I don't know.
- [Crow] Dust, need to get
Hazel in here to clean.
- [Joel] Diamonds on my windshield,
and they're tears from heaven.
I'm rollin' into town on the interstate.
Only to find Gideon's Bible.
- [Tom] I may be a secret
agent but there are places
even I won't look.
Mm, mm.
(chuckles)
I'll just take this.
I take one thing from each
apartment I break into.
I figure that's fair.
- [Crow] Andre Gregory?
But why?
- [Tom] Should be Wally
Shawn on the other one.
- [Joel] Oh so that's where
he keeps his aunt and uncle, huh?
- [Tom] I know Ron Carter's
around here somewhere.
- [Crow] Hm?
Hello Uhura.
(pistol fires)
- [Joel] Ooh.
(guns firing)
Ooh, quick get it under cold water!
- [Crow] You've been eating french fries
with Maury Mascovitz, haven't you?
Oh, he didn't flush.
- [Joel] Ooh.
- [Crow] Ooh.
- [Joel] I hope you're satisfied.
Jeez, that hurts.
- [Tom] Oh,
shot him with a knife.
Oh, this car has that
neat pasta maker option.
(buzzing)
- [Crow] It's WWalter Winchell.
- Yes, what is it?
- [Bryan] It's me Super Dragon.
- [Joel] Super Dragon, who?
- How did you enjoy your trip?
- Well they gave me a warm welcome.
I've made my mind up.
- [Tom] I'm gonna keep my baby.
- I'm gonna take Jackson's assignment.
I'll need an assistant.
How 'bout Babyface?
- Babyface?
- [Joel] But he's three.
- You want a gangster?
But he's in Sing Sing serving time
on a sentence as big as an encyclopedia.
- Well that means he knows a lot.
Get him out.
- [Tom] Hm?
- It's impossible.
- [Tom] Oh, all tangled up, agh.
- Analyze it?
There's absolutely nothing
in that stick of chewing gum.
Our scientists haven't been able to find
the smallest trace of drug in it.
- [Joel] And it just
bothers me, that's all.
It's just-
- If there is one,
it's tasteless,
odorless
and leaves no trace in the human body.
- [Crow] Velveeta?
- How many have taken
a dose of this poison
without knowing it?
And why is the drug being
handed out among minors?
Cooper, why is the drug
being circulated gratis?
That's what I wanna know.
There's no profit in it.
There must be an ulterior motive.
- [Tom] Is this part of my review?
- That's what we've got to find out.
What is it?
And who are the distributors?
What are they after?
- [Joel] Uh, delicious fruit flavor, sir.
- Don't know that yet.
But it must be pretty
important if they're willing
to leave behind them a string of corpses.
We have one clue.
Christine Brueder
and she seems to have escaped.
All the import documents,
all the Ming vases found in Ross' room.
They all seem to point to one city.
- [Crow] Circle Pines.
- Amsterdam.
- [Crow] Oh.
- When to leave?
- Now.
(jingling)
- [Joel] From the line of
secret agent Super Dragon toys.
- [Crow] Andy Devine.
- Baby.
- Here I am.
- Baby, you old warhorse, how are ya' huh?
- [Tom] A brother's touch.
- Hey you're uh,
you're getting a little
fat living upstate,
aren't ya' huh?
- You know how it is,
you go soft up in Sing Sing.
I need a vacation.
- Things may get hot.
- It's better than being on ice.
- Hm.
- Remember he's not a permanent gift.
You will return him at
the end of the assignment
and don't forget it.
- Okay.
- [Tom] Okay.
- Good luck to both of you.
- Thanks.
- [Joel] Uh, what was
our assignment again?
- Hey speaking of gifts,
and you don't have to return that one.
- And you?
- I got the twin.
- They're not hot are they?
- I built it with my own hand.
I got a patent on it.
- [Crow] Mm, same pink, different day.
- Everything's inside,
passports, money,
identification of the agents in Amsterdam.
Officially, you're a lawyer looking for
Christine Brueder
concerning an inheritance.
- Well, well done agent Popel.
- [Tom] Agent Popo?
- [Crow] Do not worship false eyelashes.
- Bryan,
I had a dream.
I dreamt I was in a
field of tulips with you.
- Sometimes dreams--
- [Joel] Ah!
- [Crow] Gah!
♫ Wonderful wonderful Copenhagen ♫
(humming)
- [Joel] Well what do ya',
(chuckles)
only the Dutch.
(laughs)
(bells chiming)
- Excuse me, do you speak English?
(Crow speaking foreign language)
- Perhaps some French, no?
- Nay.
- Italian?
- [Woman] Nay.
- Some other time.
- [Crow] Nay.
- [Joel] Hey, does anybody
else hear these bells?
- [Crow] No, this town
can get pretty annoying.
- [Joel] The prison.
- [Tom] They got kind of a weird
miniature golf course on
the second floor up there.
- [Crow] It's called The Family Circus,
see Billy drew this strip, that's...
- [Tom] Hm.
- [Joel] Boy I sure would
like to tilt at that, huh?
- [Crow] Hm.
(circus music)
(doors closing)
(Tom humming)
- Man, I don't know, Tom,
this Secret Agent Super Dragon music
that you turned into a song
doesn't look that commercial to me.
- It ain't supposed to be commercial man,
it's jazz.
- Well how would you
describe jazz anyway, Tom?
- Oh man,
if you have to ask, you'll never know.
- Yeah, whatever.
Let's go, let's wail!
- Right, Daddy.
One, two,
one, two, three, four.
♫ Secret agent
(horn honks)
♫ Super Dragon ♫
Take it Crow Daddy.
♫ Secret agent
(horn honks)
♫ Super Dragon ♫
- Yeah grab an eight, Joel.
♫ Secret agent
(horn honks)
♫ Super Dragon ♫
- Look at me now.
♫ Secret agent ♫
- Uh, wait a second.
I mean it just goes on like that, huh?
- Uh, oh,
Crow takes a trumpet solo now.
- Uh, I only picked up the
trumpet a few minutes ago.
I only know two notes.
- Well, it's not my fault if
your chops ain't together.
- Hey chop on this pal.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Oh, how'd you like a
marimba up yours huh?
- Wait a second, wait a second,
cut it out guys.
Listen I've got an idea.
Just keep playing and
singing like you were
and I'll add some spice, trust me.
- Okay, from the top babies.
♫ Secret agent
(horn honks)
♫ Super Dragon ♫
- Yeah with action.
(mimics explosions)
♫ Secret agent
(mimics machine gun firing)
♫ Super Dragon ♫
- With romance.
(kissing)
♫ Secret agent
(honks horn)
♫ Super Dragon ♫
- Intrigue.
(mimics machine gun firing)
♫ Secret agent
(honks horn)
♫ Super Dragon ♫
- With boats.
(mimics boat engine)
♫ Secret agent
(horn honks)
♫ Super Dragon ♫
- Oh baby, baby, baby, baby,
I killed that fat barkeep,
baby, baby, baby.
(mimics kissing)
Oh sorry guys, I--
- Joel man, you are really out there.
It took courage to do what you did, baby.
You took a risk, you stepped out there
on the cutting edge
and you failed miserably.
Now could we please do it
the way I wrote it, please?
♫ Secret agent
(horn honks)
(Servo scat singing)
♫ Super Dragon
♫ Secret agent ♫
- My bots are terminally hip
but I love 'em anyway.
We'll be right back, man.
♫ Super Dragon ♫
(Servo scat singing)
♫ Secret agent
♫ Secret Agent Super Dragon
♫ Super Dragon ♫
- [Bryan] Look at it closely.
- [Tom] Look at it.
- No doubt about it.
- [Joel] It's a photograph.
- He's been following me for days.
- [Babyface] Uh can I come in?
- What is it?
- I want to show you these little toys I--
- [Crow] No!
- [Joel] No!
- Oh but if I'm in the way--
- No, no, stay, stay, stay.
- Introduce the bodyguard.
- Mhm, this is Babyface.
This is Charity Farrel.
Elias Rembrandt 13.
- [Tom] Oh well that, huh?
- Our man in Holland.
- [Tom] Say.
- Ah, well,
I see we're in good shape, um,
how are you, Charity?
Well how are things?
- Like the country.
- [Tom] Huh?
- Flat.
- Well I don't think
you'll be bored with us.
- [Joel] It's a joke, forget it.
- What do you know
about Christine Brueder?
- [Crow] Secret agent
Superrude if you ask me.
- Been to see her?
- Yes but nobody answers there.
- Porter?
- There are no porters in Holland.
- Well that's a good thing to know.
- [Joel] Oh shut up M. Emmet Walsh.
- Excuse me.
- Neighbors?
- [Woman] They don't know anything.
- Men in her life?
- [Joel] Mennonites?
- [Woman] Quite a few.
- Most important?
- Lamas.
- [Tom] Fernando or Lorenzo?
- A venerable millionaire, mad for her.
The mask you sent me was the one that
Christine wore at his
masked ball last year.
- Good.
We'll start with him.
- It's already done.
Senor Lamas is receiving
attorney Bryan Cooper
tomorrow at 10.
- Fine.
I think we'll get along all right.
- Anything else?
- Yes, one little thing.
Are you a natural redhead?
- [Crow] Are you a natural blackhead?
- You'll have to take my word for it.
For now.
- [Joel] Wait are you saying,
does that mean I'm,
uh, bye.
- [Crow] Oh flat, I get it.
- You know what I always said,
dames are like safes,
some guys know their secrets
and some guys don't.
- Is that what you've always said?
- Yeah.
- I think you've spent too
much time cracking safes.
(Tom mimics drumbeat
- [Joel] Why there's Amsterdam.
- [Tom] Hey Maury!
Oh, oh.
- [Joel] Hey his eyes have a zoom feature.
- I think it's time we made
a couple of social calls.
Let's start with Christine Brueder.
- All right.
- [Tom] Now why did he bring this guy?
- I made you an outfit
special for the occasion.
- [Crow] It's a bulletproof teddy.
- It's the coolest thing going
and absolutely bulletproof.
(chuckles)
- [Joel] This won't go
with my black skirt.
- Well what did you want, huh?
Buttons and bows?
- [Tom] Oh there's a satin
tap pant that goes with it.
- Ah and while we're on
the subject of buttons--
- [Tom] They shoulda brought Jack Weston.
- Looks just like the others.
- [Joel] He's kind of a
white trash Q, isn't he?
- [Crow] Yeah.
It's ingenious, it closes your jacket.
- All right.
- [Tom] Okay now,
I'm the escaped convict
and you're the warden's wife.
- Perfect fit, huh?
- [Joel] It's a little tight in the busom.
- And what's this for?
- This
is the safety.
- [Crow] Are they going steady now?
- That's it.
- It seems to work all right.
- Hey, now tell me I'm not a genius.
- [Bryan] All right.
You're not a genius.
- [Joel] Hey I walked right into that one.
- [Tom] Ba boom.
- [Crow] Well now he's
secret agent Superloiterer.
- [Man] There you are.
- [Tom] Laramie, is that you?
- [Joel] Andy Capp's gained weight.
- Is it busted?
- No it isn't.
(Tom humming)
- [Crow] I know what you're wearing.
- [Tom] Boy, they've
seen a lot of apartments
on this trip, haven't they?
- [Joel] Hey it's Rula Lenska's place.
- [Crow] I hope this isn't
like a John Waters film
and they lick all the furniture.
- [Tom] Tub Taylor on vibes.
- [Crow] Hm, Broytans.
- [Joel] Here, try opening the top.
Gimme that.
- [Tom] Well I,
I loosened it for ya'.
- [Joel] Oh I didn't get you anything.
- [Crow] He's wearing the
Phil Harris collection.
- [Joel] Oh no, it's grandma's brag book.
- Here, you keep the
picture of Vic Tayback.
(mysterious music)
(humming)
- [Joel] I'm just gonna
freshen up in here, okay?
- [Crow] I enjoy being a girl.
Huh, oh.
- [Tom] Ladies and
gentlemen, Mother Teresa.
- [Crow] (gasps) Hey.
- [Tom] Maybe not.
- Are you looking for somewhere to sleep,
or something else?
- [Bryan] No, I was feeling a
little bit lonely, that's all.
- Did you think I would keep you company?
- Something like that, yes.
- [Crow] Do you have a towel I can borrow?
- That might have been your idea
but you've come to the wrong address.
Give me my robe.
- Oh, sure.
- [Woman] Stay where you are.
- [Joel] Lay down.
- Would you turn your
face to the wall please?
- Oh no, I don't mind turning.
I like all kinds of games.
(Babyface whistles)
- [Crow] Oooh pretty lady.
- [Woman] And who is this?
- Who him?
Why I never saw that
man before in my life.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
What do you think you're doing in this
nice lady's bedroom?
Why don't you get out
of here, you stupid oaf?
Get out of here.
- Okay, okay, I'm going.
I got the wrong door.
- [Tom] Allen and Rossi,
ladies and gentlemen,
Allen and Rossi.
- [Crow] With Julie Budd.
- [Woman] And you, what
are you waiting for?
- Well, a little information
if you don't mind.
Do you uh,
happen to know this girl, hm?
- Why yes, it's Christine Brueder,
she's living here with me.
What do you want to know for?
- I happen to be a lawyer.
I'm here on a very important
inheritance problem.
My name is Bryan Cooper.
- [Joel] Cooper like the hockey equipment.
- I'm sorry but Christine's
not in Amsterdam.
She's away with some friends.
- Do you happen to know
when she'll be getting back?
- I imagine if she's having fun,
it will be a while.
- Well I'd like to see
her some day when she's
not so busy amusing herself.
- But please, next time ring the bell.
Leave me your address in
case my friend returns.
- [Tom] They talk like
a Speed Racer cartoon.
- Sure, sure, here you are.
Hope I see you again, hm?
- [Crow] Hey, secret agent's crossed out
and lawyer's written in.
Hm.
(dialing)
- [Joel] You're on Larry King Live,
Europe, you're on the air.
- Please Alex,
you've got to listen carefully.
- [Joel] Yeah, I know,
I look like Spike Jonze.
- You must do it.
He's very dangerous.
That's right, just do what I tell you.
- [Crow] Go to the window.
- Yes you must.
- [Joel] Increase your bust.
- [Tom] Oh enough spy crap,
time to see Amsterdam.
(laughs)
(happy music)
Brideshead revisited.
To the manor Borne.
Upstairs, downstairs,
the magician with Bill Bixby.
- [Crow] Huh?
- [Man] That's the last picture of her
over a year ago.
- [Crow] She has a beard now.
- [Joel] Mario Cuomo?
- Christine and I were very good friends.
- [Crow] Nobody in this movie knows
when to stop decorating.
- [Tom] Uh, you got any art here?
- Then all of a sudden-
- [Joel] Kablooey.
- The girl I thought I
knew became a stranger.
Moody, withdrawn.
I found out she'd begun to drug herself.
I tried to get her to stop it.
She wouldn't.
She booked passage for America.
Now you say that she's returned.
- [Crow] But good luck
with your pledge drive.
- I'd have expected her to telephone.
- [Tom] Wanna give this a try?
- Are you having an auction
masquerade this year?
- Yes, I wouldn't miss it for anything.
- [Joel] Except cheese.
- This year I'm offering a canvas
that's rather extraordinary.
You're a lover of the arts, aren't you?
- Well I'm afraid all I
can afford is to look.
(laughs)
- [Tom] Get out!
- May I show you my lute
player by Franz Haus?
- [Tom] No, no, no, no, please.
- It's the prize of the entire collection.
- [Tom] Emo avec lute.
- It's worth over a million Dutch florins.
But I expect it to
raise considerably more.
No, it'll all be for charity.
I think you'll find this interesting.
- [Crow] But stupid.
- Over here.
- [Tom] Get in this.
- It's an international
hospital for babies
with malnutrition.
- [Joel] And pancakes.
- Art is a marvelous thing.
But saving lives,
children's lives especially--
- [Crow] It's not that good.
- Is more important.
That's why I always try to
make my auctions spectacular.
It appeals to everyone's vanity.
- [Joel] And Apollonia too.
- Generosity, as you know, is rare.
Vanity on the other hand,
is a rather common trait.
- Yes, but the vain like to be seen
and your parties are
masquerades, aren't they?
(Tom chuckles)
- That makes it a little more exciting.
The losers can remain anonymous.
- [Crow] And the winners
remain bottomless.
- And when the winner removes his mask,
there is usually applause
and his vanity is satisfied completely.
- Oh that's most ingenious,
but I'm afraid we've taken
up too much of your time.
- Not at all.
Very grateful to you for your visit.
- [Joel] Um, what else, oh.
- We're all anxious to locate Christine.
I've every hope we can.
We'll keep in touch.
- [Woman] You've been most kind.
- And thank you.
- [Tom] Oh and let us know
when the Pavarotti comes in.
- There's a famous hotel in Wallendam.
- [Joel] Called the Shady Rest.
- Christine used to go
there frequently, I recall.
You might try that.
- Thank you.
- [Crow] But don't eat
the almonds in the bar,
they charge you 10 bucks for them.
- You look a little discouraged.
- Looks like I brought
you on a wild goose chase.
- Oh there's nothing to worry about.
- [Tom] I like geese, uh oh.
- Christine was pretty
well known at Lamas' place,
I suppose.
- [Joel] Fernando or Lorenzo?
- Why don't you pick up four
tickets to the fair, huh?
- Four?
You plan to bring a friend?
- Sure, the joker.
When I play,
you see?
I always have one up my sleeve.
- The joker?
- You'd better reserve a room for tonight
in a quiet hotel
someplace out of the city.
I'm taking a little trip to Volendam.
I could get lucky.
- [Crow] (chuckles)
Lucky (chuckles), get it?
That was a joke.
(chuckles)
- Allow me.
- [Tom] I better get going.
- I'll see you tonight?
- See you at my place.
Before your joker arrives.
- [Joel] (laughs) Oh boy, that
kid's got personality plus.
- [Crow] Picture, picture's
showing us Holland.
- [Joel] Pannekoeken.
- Uh, excuse me?
- [Tom] Hi, do you have
any dolls or postcards?
- Hotel Spander is?
(woman speaking foreign language)
- (mutters) Thanks a lot.
- Souvenir of Volendam?
- [Tom] You want me so bad.
- [Crow] Damn secret
super jerk if you ask me.
- [Joel] Here give this to Audrey Hepburn.
(soothing music)
- [Crow] Oh, I'm so embarrassed,
she wore the same thing as me.
- [Tom] Hi, do you know where
I could find some knick knacks
or curios with kind of a Holland theme?
- [Crow] Cheese.
- [Joel] Oh somebody put me up to this.
I hate this.
- [Tom] Tonight, music box danger.
- Christine Brueder?
Yes,
she was one of my best customers.
She came here almost every night
and brought her whole crowd with her.
- Well uh,
did you ever happen to
see this man in the group?
- [Crow] Hey that's dirty.
- Well I'm not sure.
No, I don't know him.
There were always so many of them.
Since they stopped coming,
this place has been like a morgue.
- [Joel] Except for all those customers.
- Don't you worry honey.
I think maybe you got
yourself a live one, hm?
Can I use the phone?
- Help yourself.
Marika.
- [Joel] Now what?
- Ya, Miss Truda?
- Please help this
gentleman to find the phone.
- Ya this way please.
- Don't forget to come and see me again.
- How could I forget?
- [Crow] Well, you're a secret agent.
You have a lot on your mind.
- [Joel] Hey anywhere I can
go to soak up the local color?
- There you are.
- [Tom] I gotta drain the superdragon.
- [Crow] Och mein God, he's smooth.
- American embassy?
Let me have 223.
- Yes.
- [Bryan] Cooper speaking.
Send the following cable,
Derrick-
- [Joel] It's a Franco-American flag.
- [Bryan] Fulton's presence
required for Brueder heir, stop.
Cooper.
- Yes, okay Mr. Cooper, right away.
- [Tom] I still got it.
- [Crow] Uh, hey you're
out of paper there.
- [Tom] Hm, uh,
oh well, here goes (inhales).
(buzzing)
- [Joel] I know somebody
who borrowed a pants suit
from Hope Lange.
(Tom sexily growls)
(buzzing)
Oh.
- I hope Mr. Cooper will excuse
me for keeping him waiting.
I just threw on a little something
to make myself presentable.
- Well I really don't mind waiting at all
as long as I think the
results are good but um,
I was expecting Rembrandt 13.
- But it's Ms. Farrow
who's receiving tonight.
Please, will you come in?
- [Crow] Hangin' with Mr. Cooper.
- [Tom] Oh you should've
seen all the quaint stuff
I saw today.
(chuckles) Boy that Holland.
- Did you catch anything in Volendam?
- I think I caught a little bit of a cold.
- [Crow] Get ready, he's
gonna steal her cigarette.
- You're not going to talk about work now?
- I'm afraid we're going to have to.
- [Tom] Well Bernice
in the cube next to me
is such a gossip.
- All right I'll get you the file.
Would you get us some drinks, please?
- [Joel] Yup, he did it again.
- I'll take a bourbon.
- [Joel] Uh, me too thanks, oh.
- [Crow] Ew, tastes like catnip.
- [Joel] He's putting it out on the couch.
- [Tom] Hey, uh, got any magazines?
(humming)
- [Joel] I'm gonna bend at
the waist someday, I know it.
- [Tom] Uh, Christmas
time, slaughterhouse friend
dime arrears?
- [Joel] He's a slow reader.
- [Crow] (chuckles) I'm the
best thing in this message.
- [Joel] Man, I'm smug.
- [Tom] (humming) Hey, how
much longer are you gonna be?
What'd you fall in?
- [Joel] Anybody know what's going on?
- [Crow] Boy this really
ties into the whole
chewing gum thing.
- [Tom] Maybe I should open a curio shop.
(humming)
- [Joel] 'Bout time.
- [Crow] I wasn't doin' nothin'.
- [Joel] You know in that
light she looks just like
Geddy Lee.
(Crow groans)
- [Tom] I thought you were
gonna change, what gives?
- [Joel] Should a gentleman offer a lady
a Tiparillo?
- [Crow] She got tall all of a sudden.
- [Tom] Bet she can probably really feel
the smoothness now.
Never mind.
- [Joel] Boy she must be
getting paid a lot of money.
- [Tom] Something intoxicating
happens when Brylcreem
and white shoulders meet, you know?
(power drains)
- [Crow] Oh that happens
to everyone now and again.
- [Tom] Oh.
- [Joel] Oh he should follow
through on something for once.
- [Tom] We gotta go.
- This happens very
often in this district.
I'll get a flashlight.
(happy music)
- People, places.
Oh good.
Uh well if you've all had a
chance to look over the script,
let's start on--
- Crow this better not be another stupid
Earth versus soup type
of spec script, buddy.
- Tom, I think you'll
be pleasantly surprised.
I've streamlined, chopped
and channeled the spy movie genre
to reflect nineties sensibilities.
- Well you know, Crow, that
sounds really interesting.
- Thank you, Joel.
The market demands it you know.
Tom, you'll be reading the
part of Sandy Wyndhamhill,
the good looking in an androgynous way,
super spy who is in touch
with his feminine side.
I realize I'm asking you to
play against type but I think-
- Gee that sounds really,
stupid Crow.
I can't foil the evil forces
trying to conquer the world
if I'm a dumb old sissy britches.
- Wait a minute.
Servo, let's just give it a chance.
We'll just read Crow's treatment, okay?
- The Spy Who Hugged Me.
Joel, you'll be reading a
couple of parts if you would.
Sandy's love interest, Holly Affirmations
and the bad guy,
Gary Diabolique.
- For god's sake man.
I wanna drink martini's in Istanbul
and order glib (mumbles) in Moscow
and drive with my feet
while escaping thugs
in Monte Carlo and meet girls in Ipanema.
The kind of things a
super secret super spy
is supposed to do.
- I support your owning those feelings.
- Yeah support this.
- Top of page 12, Joel,
you're Holly.
- Okay.
You understand, Mr. Wyndamhill,
that even though we are
sharing a sexual tension
between us, I must kill you.
- Um, Holly, thank you for being honest.
Let me say that I think
you're a really terrific
dynamite lady but right now I'm in a
committed relationship with someone
who is very special to me?
I don't believe this.
- Okay, Holly pulls a
gun out of her purse,
I'll use my hand
and says,
then you understand, Mr. Wyndhamhill,
nothing personal.
- Uh, boundaries, Holly, boundaries.
Crow, I'm supposed to be a man who
leads a life of danger.
- Servo, the only way around it
is through it.
- Oh brother.
- Okay,
let's jump ahead a few pages.
Sandy has carpooled with Gary Diabolique
to the world domination headquarters
and Joel
you're Gary and you're going to
shame the world
with your specially invented
anti-Bradshaw device.
So top of page 26
and Thomas.
- Okay (clears throat).
Mr. Diabolique if you have a few minutes
I need to confront you
on your shaming behavior.
- Oh Mr. Big Wyndhamhill,
thinks he's going to save the world.
Well who do you think you are, mister?
- Um, Gary, I feel you're upset with me.
I know it's not about me
but about issues in your family of origin.
You have got to be kidding me, Crow.
- Uh, so you think you know everything
Mr. Namby Pamby Damby butt.
Gonna cry now, huh?
Gonna cry?
- Um, I have to ask you
to respect my boundaries.
- You don't get it, do you?
You stupid moron idiot.
I'm going to control how
people respond to me.
I am going to rule the world.
- Gary, that's really codependent.
I can't believe I just said codependent!
That's it.
You completely defiled
a revered film archetype
and you made me feel like a total buffoon.
I'm out of here.
- Well, really only Tom
can make Tom feel like
a total buffoon.
- [Tom] Ah, bite me.
(sirens blare)
- Ah, we got movie sign!
(doors opening)
- [Crow] Oh there he is.
Oh good an action sequence!
- [Tom] Finally.
- [Crow] And it's over.
(Tom chuckles)
- [Joel] There he goes,
and a classic Jackie Chan disarm.
- All right, now who sent you, huh?
- [Tom] Oh right, your bourbon.
Does this answer your question?
(dramatic music)
- You take it easy.
- [Joel] I take it anyway I can.
- He hasn't talked yet.
- [Tom] Hey that's my gum.
- [Joel] Oh no, now we'll never know
if Razzles are candy or gum.
- Cyanide.
- [Tom] It's like poison or something.
- Everybody dies too quickly in this mess.
I'd better get rid of him.
- [Tom] Do you have a
garbage bag or somethin'?
- [Joel] Hey, he's a lot
lighter than I thought.
- [Tom] He's hollow.
- [Crow] Uh, just set him anywhere.
- [Tom] Going down, Mr. Interloper?
(water splashes)
- [Joel] Hey, he made the pool.
- [Crow] It's so convenient
to have a river so close.
- [Tom] Oh yeah.
Well back at it.
- [Joel] Amsterdam I'm good.
- [Crow] Hm, yeah,
now, where were my lips?
Oh yeah, huh.
- [Joel] You know, I don't
think I could go back
to kissing after someone
just died in my apartment.
- [Crow] Yeah, I'd need a
while to pull myself together.
- [Tom] Sure, a couple of days.
- [Crow] No, a couple of minutes.
- [Joel] Well he seems to
be taking it all right.
- [Crow] So does she.
- You still afraid?
- [Tom] Yes, no, pass.
- [Crow] Oh no I hope
their chins don't lock.
- [Tom] Oh I get it, the car,
a brick road (laughs).
Driving.
- [Joel] Sonny Corleone, watch out.
(mimics machine guns)
- [Tom] Hello, any talent to declare?
- [Joel] Huh, he seemed nice.
(mysterious saxophone music)
(Crow humming)
(Tom humming)
- [Tom] Plastiface, a
division of Cumhugecone.
- [Crow] Strangely enough,
it's an unfinished furniture place.
(all humming)
- [Tom] Oh.
I think you need to take a rest in Ward E.
(humming)
- [Joel] Oh this thing.
- [Tom] Oh it tickles.
(laughs)
(alarm going off)
- [Crow] Oh, ha, that's my
zucchini wrapped in foil.
- [Joel] I'm an actuary
and I still have to go through this thing.
- [Tom] There, happy?
Now I'm sterile again.
- [Crow] Ah, good morning Mr. Solo.
- [Joel] All this to get
to the vending machines.
- [Tom] Looks like he
only has one message.
- [Crow] Come on, come on!
- [Tom] Oh it's Jack Lord again.
- [Joel] It's Herb from Burger King.
- [Crow] Could something
please just happen?
- [Tom] Oh, can't get out now.
- [Joel] Aw, I just
forgot something, okay?
- Don't sit down yet, Alex.
- [Tom] The chair's still wet.
- Do you realize how
many times you've failed
in your mission?
- [Crow] 12?
Oh it's rhetorical.
- [Joel] Uh, does this have
to be an all staff sir?
(alarm beeping)
- [Tom] Hm, oh what's that?
Didn't know about that.
- [Crow] Would somebody
answer the table please?
I'll get it.
- [Joel] Pretty cool, huh?
I just had that put in.
- [Tom] What's it take?
Couple of nine-volts?
- [Voiceover] Professor Kruger,
I read your report and I am satisfied
with the results obtained so far.
- [Crow] Remind your engineers
to use coasters on me.
- [Voiceover] But we must
make more rapid progress.
- [Joel] Pick up the pace, chop, chop.
- [Voiceover] Doctor Misimoto.
- [Tom] Oh sorry, I wasn't listening.
- [Voiceover] You have not yet succeeded
in perfecting a universal catalyst
for Synchron 2.
- [Joel] Well, it's hard.
- [Voiceover] I'll give
you four days more.
- [Crow] Study now, or lat, oh.
- [Voiceover] Alex.
- [Joel] What's with your hair?
- [Voiceover] A third American spy
is arriving in Amsterdam.
I should be sorry to have to replace you
but if you fail me again
I shall have no choice.
Regarding Christine Bruder,
she has served her purpose.
- [Tom] That table's really
callin' him on the carpet.
- All right, I won't fail you.
- [Crow] Leonard Cohen at home.
(Joel mimics farting)
(laughing)
- Agent Fulton at your service.
Something I can do for you?
- [Crow] Yeah, comb your hair.
- You can make out my will.
- First tell me that
you're glad to see me.
- I'm thrilled to see you.
- Once again, very nicely.
- [Tom] Here, let me unbunch you.
- [Joel] Wow, looks
like they're making out
in Peter Brady's room.
- [Tom] So when's my review?
(phone rings)
- [Crow] Wow, she's responsive.
- Hello.
- [Voiceover] You'd better come down.
We found Christine, I'll be in the bar.
- Huh, okay, okay.
I'm sorry sweetheart.
- Business or pleasure?
- It's Rembrandt 13 calling.
- Then it's business.
- You haven't seen Rembrandt 13.
- [Joel] She looks like a
white member of the Supremes.
- Who's Comfort?
- A real luscious blonde.
- Oh, that's the joker.
- Joker?
- Well.
- [Tom] Looking for Mr. Goodbar?
- She's at the central clinic.
They called Lamas and he
let me know immediately.
- We better get there right away, come on.
- [Tom] Come on.
- [Joel] Fashions from the
Lollipop Guild collection.
- Not bad huh?
- [Crow] If you like that sort of thing.
- Bet that red hair came out of a bottle.
- [Tom] Ha, look who's talking.
(burps)
- A martini, please.
- [Joel] Now that comes out of a bottle.
- Two martinis.
- [Woman] I don't wanna die, help me.
You've got to.
- [Crow] I don't want to
die, I don't want to die.
Look I've got problems too.
- Hin Kron,
hurry.
- [Joel] Please bring me a pizza.
This hospital food's crap.
(woman sighs)
- [Tom] Very comforting.
- [Crow] Yeah, he's got
a good deadside manner.
- [Doctor] There's no way to save her.
- [Joel] Okay bye.
- [Voiceover] We don't
even know what killed her.
- [Crow] Gum?
- [Tom] Well there's some
things that I have to attend to,
that I have to do, the things, bye.
Science!
- Yes, what have you come for?
- [Joel] Pencils?
- Christine is dead.
You killed her by
refusing her the antidote.
After all she had done for you
and the same will happen to me.
- [Tom] You seem upset.
- Yes it could.
Super Dragon is not yet eliminated.
- [All] Ew!
- Because you failed.
- I don't want to kill anybody.
Until now, I've done everything for you.
Even against my will.
You have got to keep your promise
and free me from this drug.
- [Crow] Hey how'd they do that?
- Impressionable.
- [Tom] They're both doing
Shelly Birman routines.
- I saw that man again.
Yes.
- [Joel] What's that lump on his chest?
- So you followed him.
- Of course but he managed to get away.
- [Crow] I'm not that good
at following yet. (laughs)
- His being at the clinic makes me believe
that this girl didn't die a natural death.
What's more, they're going
to bury her tomorrow.
- [Tom] Don't that beat all?
- They're a little bit
too much in a hurry,
don't you think?
- Well maybe we'll beat them to it.
- [Joel] Looks great from this angle.
- I think I'll take a look
around the clinic tonight.
- [Tom] Tell him your volleyball
practice is running late.
- The service entrance
is the Prinzenhoc 16.
- Yes, I think I can find that all right.
You're always right on the ball,
aren't you sweetheart, huh?
- [Crow] Yes, I'm in a Howard Johnson.
- [Tom] (chuckles) God, I'm good.
- [Joel] Oh terrific, this guy's back.
- [Tom] Excuse me sir,
uh, where you going?
Uh, sir, I have to stamp your hand sir.
Sir.
- [Crow] Could you explain
again why I do all the work?
- This was too easy.
- Then what took you so long?
- [Joel] Hey why can't
you ever support me?
- Have a good time.
- [Tom] I'm gonna make the deposit,
I'll be right back.
- [Joel] Hm, 200 a month
plus utilities, huh?
- [Tom] A screen gems presentation.
- [Crow] You know, the other
apartments I've snooped
around are much nicer than this.
(action jazz music)
- [Joel] Wow, this is
a swingin' boiler room.
- [Crow] Yeah, it's cool.
Dig it.
(Tom humming)
- [Tom] Oh (chuckles) there it is.
The lugen, look...
- [Joel] Hooray I'm super clown!
- [Crow] I paid to see the Likenkelder
and I'm not leaving 'til I do.
- [Joel] Jim West.
- [Tom] Babyface, I'm being
beat up by longshoremen.
- [Crow] Well this isn't
bad, we'll be home in, hey!
- [Tom] This looks like the
end of Romancing the Stone.
It's not funny, I'm just pointing it out.
- [Crow] Looks like a
Crosby family outing.
- [Joel] Man, whatever likenkelder is
it must be pretty good.
- [Tom] Took the Nestea plunge.
(tense music)
- [Joel] It was my punch, you know.
- [Crow] Yeah, well I made him woozy.
- [Joel] Oh, he needs a
shovel proof vest there.
- [Crow] Oh, great.
- Taken care of the one outside.
Good, now we'd better get moving.
- [Tom] Yes it's Lech
Walesa and Billy Pilgrim.
- [Crow] Ha, fooled ya.
(grunts)
Maybe not.
- Stay still.
- [Tom] Boy it's a good
thing that 24 hour mortuary
is just around the corner.
- Now give me a hand with it.
(applauding)
- [Crow] Boy he sure is smooth, boss.
- [Tom] Hey he fits, last time
we had to cut the feet off.
- Screw the lid down.
- [Joel] If you wanna lock in deadness.
- [Crow] His chin looks
like a Parker House roll.
(screws tightening)
- [Tom] Not dead yet,
hey I'm feeling better.
- [Joel] You know someday
we should all go in
and buy a Makita.
- [Tom] Uh guys, this isn't funny.
Man I hate hell week.
- You better telephone the boss.
- Right.
- [Crow] Borrow me a quarter.
- [Joel] Hey he's gonna show
himself a Linda Hunt movie.
- [Crow] Good morning Mr. Phelps.
Morning Mr. Phelps, morning
Mr. Phelps, morning Mr. Phelps.
- Hello?
This is Valiki.
- [Joel] That's a great dead tires plus.
- He's ready for ya.
Yeah, ready for the burial, what?
Okay good idea.
Right boss.
- [Crow] (laughs) Guy's
actually pretty funny.
- [Tom] Okay guys I give.
Fun's over guys, fun's over.
- What are you doin'?
- The boss has had a brilliant idea
of dropping it into the canal
where it's gonna disappear
without leaving a trace.
(thugs laughing)
- [Tom] I heard that, it's not funny.
- [Man] It'll all be over in an hour.
- [Tom] Uh guys,
guys it's really hot in here.
Oh screw ya then.
(tense music)
- [Crow] Gonna time how long I live.
That'll show 'em.
- One.
- [Joel] Mississippi.
- Hour.
- [Tom] Father.
- [Joel] Hey what do you know,
something's connecting with
something else in the family.
- Okay, take that in.
- [Crow] Lift with the legs.
Good, good.
- [Tom] Oh I get it, he's
gonna lower his metabolism
like James Coburn in In Like Flynn.
(Tom humming "Funeral March" by Chopin)
Come on guys let's do the song.
(humming)
Come on.
- [Crow] Okay, okay,
lean your end a little.
There you go, grab that end.
Okay, good, good.
- [Tom] Oh my knees.
- [Joel] You know you find
yourself doing the weirdest
things in this business.
- [Tom] Ain't that the truth.
- Right into the lake..
- [Tom] Oh and this guy's dead,
we don't gotta buy him no ticket.
- [Joel] But there was no monster.
- [Crow] Here at Gordon DeGlosta
we bury our corpses fresh.
Never expected this to happen.
- [Tom] Oh you mean he's still alive?
Wow.
- [Crow] Hey what's he doin'?
Stop that.
- [Tom] He's bad.
- [Crow] Naughty.
- [Joel] Old Dutch, the snappy chip.
Crispy, crunchy, light and.
- [Tom] Windmills were
held stationary today
in tribute to the death of
secret agent Super Dragon.
- [Joel] They are so
incredibly in Holland, man.
- [Tom] Mhm.
Well they shouldn't have
taken the harbor excursion
boat to do this.
- [Crow] We commit the
body to the deep, dump him.
- Okay boys there he goes.
- [Tom] Ha, fooled ya,
I wasn't breathing, whoa, whoa,
just filling the lungs up with water.
I'm in for it now,
didn't wanna do that.
- Bon voyage.
- [Joel] Charlie Brown.
(mysterious music)
- [Crow] (yawns) I'm tired.
Think I'll sleep with the fishes.
- [Joel] Ouch, owie.
- [Crow] Heh, only way he could foil us
is if he reduced his breathing.
- [Tom] Oh don't even think
about, heh, about doing that.
- [Crow] Yeah, you're right,
let's go have a Grolsch.
- [Tom] Ah, sure sounds good.
(happy music)
(tense music)
♫ Somewhere
♫ Beyond the sea ♫
- [Tom] At least he has his cash card.
- [Joel] Conrad Pooh and
his inflatable knees.
- [Tom] He is George Jetson.
- [Crow] I see their white belly.
- [Tom] Oh no, I'm gonna, ow!
- [Joel] Oh this must be in the Brookstone
hard to find tool catalog.
(buzzing)
(scratching)
Ah, that noise.
- [Tom] A fork on a plate.
- [Crow] Free, it's me (coughs),
what's my time on this one?
- [Tom] They're doing all this in front of
a starving artist's painting here.
Back there, yup.
- Did you sleep well Bryan?
- [Joel] Oh very frigging
funny, Tom Wicker.
- The bedding was a bit damp
and the service was lousy but
it could've been a lot
worse if it hadn't been
for your help.
- And now everybody thinks we're dead.
- That might work out
better than you think.
- [Crow] Thanks peanut.
- [Tom] April 11th,
dear diary, he's dead.
I can now love Stan.
Finally came to terms with the hair.
Oh, and I found the perfect clown suit
to wear around the house.
- Carmen to Bryan Cooper.
Conditions in Fremont worse.
Hundreds of students taken
to psychiatric clinics, stop.
- [Crow] Don't stop.
- So far, impossible to hold--
- [Crow] Stop.
- Sickness progress, stop.
Ming vases found Ross
home false and fabricated
with unknown substance, stop.
Absolutely urgent, learn
drug formula for antidote.
- [Tom] Is it a humorous antidote?
(chuckles)
Hey anybody wanna go bowlin'?
Or somethin'?
- [Woman] I don't wanna die, help me.
You've got to, please.
- [Tom] Mary had a little lamb.
Her fleece.
- [Woman] Hurry.
(groaning)
- [Joel] Hey it's Donna Summer.
- [Tom] Hm, what do you know.
- [Crow] Probably uses his reel-to-reel
to light his cigarette.
- Anti-synchron.
That's the antidote.
Anti-synchron.
Christine was drugged by
the same drug the kids
in Fremont got.
- But who's got this anti-synchron?
- [Joel] Yeah let's drop
this and bowl a few frames.
- This should tell us.
Page,
four.
- [Tom] And huzzah it's gone.
- Three,
two,
zero, dial it.
- Me?
- Yeah go ahead, we're
supposed to be dead.
- Who do I ask for?
- [Crow] Ah just whoever answers is fine.
- Charity Farrel.
- [Joel] And then just hang up quick.
- [Tom] It might really
help if they'd let us in
on the plot.
Don't you think?
- [Crow] Could you stand
a little closer, please?
- [Tom] She's modeling the
Florence Henderson collection, I see.
(phone rings)
- [Joel] Uh, your pen is ringing, sir.
- [Crow] My table's a guy,
my pen is a phone, I'm nuts.
- Yes, who's there?
- [Woman] I'd like to speak
to Charity Farrel please.
- [Tom] It's an office,
why does he have to disguise the phone?
- There isn't anyone here called Charity,
you have the wrong number.
- [Joel] Uh, am I on speakerpen?
- Okay, now call on Mrs. Gleiss,
use the introduction we agreed upon, call.
Three, six.
- [Crow] Tell anybody about my pen
and I'll have to kill you.
- Did you give her this number?
- No, never.
(phone rings)
- [Tom] Answer the chaffing dish.
- [Joel] Uh, it's a great
day at House of Art.
- Star's house.
Come for 10?
- [Tom] Oh that's for me,
I'll take it on the pencil sharpener.
- Yes.
- [Crow] Yes, yes I'm wearing
a sleeveless tank top.
- Just a moment please.
- [Tom] (clears throat) Rod!
Oh, you're right there. (chuckles)
- Her American friends,
Cooper and the other one,
promised her an invitation at the auction
and now she can't find them anywhere.
- [Joel] Oh and friends
are visiting from Europe.
- Good morning, yes?
- [Tom] Yes.
- Yes, my secretary mentioned it.
- [Crow] Yes, just a
burgundy sweater with a tie.
- Very well, I'll send you an invitation.
Hotel Rutake.
Splendid.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think you'll like our entertainment,
so goodbye.
- [Joel] That's how you
handle a superdragon.
- Our friend is in for a surprise.
(Tom chuckles)
- Only after we learn
where she got that number.
(Tom laughs maniacally)
- Well from here on out sweetheart,
I'm afraid they're going
to put the finger on you.
- [Crow] Like a cigarette, boss?
- You seem to be the only
surviving American agent
who knows who Lamas is.
- Thanks a lot.
- Yeah but you'll have us
two covering you from behind.
- [Joel] Ah, you've
been in prison too long.
- In other words, I have to serve as bait.
- That's right
and I hope you try to
be very attractive bait.
- I'll try.
- [Tom] Ms. Collagen Lips.
- [Crow] Welcome to the
Fred Murtz Mystery Cafe.
- [Tom] See, they told me it
was a costume ball, that's why.
♫ Around the world in 80 days ♫
(humming)
- [Tom] Oh, you see really,
they told me it was a costume ball.
(laughs)
Boy, aren't I the perfect ass?
- [Crow] Hey looks like
it's snowin' upstairs.
(chuckles)
- [Joel] One word, Ben, plastics.
- [Tom] Hey, someone's
gotta make a keg run.
- [Crow] Okay, well just
shoot down to Belgium, man.
They're open later.
- [Tom] Yeah get the
French ambassador to go.
- [Crow] Oh no that wild
man Rainier wants to
put the new riders on again.
- [Tom] Whoo!
- [Joel] Hey come on.
Hey everybody stay out
of my parent's room.
Come on.
- [Auctioneer] 8,000 once,
8,000 twice,
sold for 8,000 florins.
- [Joel] She pulled in a good price.
- I never knew that Chinese Ming vases
could bring such a high price.
- It's a game of vanity
for a worthy cause.
- [Auctioneer] Would
you step up here, sir?
- [Crow] Number 73,
a date with Prince Phillip.
Prince Phillip.
- [Tom] Hm, sorry sir,
Telecheck says no way.
- [Crow] Would you please?
- Beautiful vases, authentic Ming.
- Yeah just like the ones in Fremont.
- [Joel] Oh that was low.
- Have you noticed how all
four vases have been bought
by men in oval masks?
- [Tom] Don't you hate that?
- You're a fortunate man.
- Thank you.
- [Bryan] Find out where he's going.
- [Tom] Got a big ol' hole in his head.
- Now ladies and gentlemen,
we offer the next to last Ming vase.
The artist who spent his
life in creating these
has evidently excelled himself
in this allegory of spring.
- [Crow] How much?
- [Auctioneer] Starting
price, a mere 3,000 florins.
- [Tom] All right then, 2,000.
- 3,500.
- 5,000.
- 5,500.
- [Crow] I've got some lupins.
- Nine.
- Seven I bid.
- 8,000 I bid.
- Eight five I bid.
- 9,000.
- [Joel] They're all dressed
as Mexican wrestlers.
- [Crow] El Santo.
- [Tom] You know, he should
put eye holes in that thing.
(romantic orchestral music)
- [Crow] Oh this is the
nicest voting booth I've seen.
Oh and it feels good too.
- [Tom] Time to go.
(doors closing)
- Hey Joel,
I've got a pretty good
handle on what's cool, right?
- That's right, you do.
- And your average spy movie
is generally pretty high
on the cool scale?
- Oh absolutely, there's nothing cooler
than being a secret agent super spy.
- Well then would you say
that this guy while lame,
is typical of most spy
guys in most spy movies?
- Yeah, well, yeah.
- Well then I have a question.
- I was hoping this was headed somewhere.
- How come this guy keeps
saying confusing stuff like,
the time he gets jumped,
which is obviously a bad thing,
he said, "They gave me
a real warm reception."
- Oh well they all go to
super secret spy school,
that's where they learned
to hone their precise skills
like how to simultaneously
attract and repel the opposite sex.
The virtues of doing
espionage in Monte Carlo
as opposed to Littleshoot, Wisconsin,
what makes turtlenecks so darn cool
and most importantly,
they take a course called
post-kill puns
and that's where you
learn to say things like,
we went for a little swim,
which means,
they tried to drown me.
- Oh now that's a cool
class, tell me more.
- Oh yeah they've got one
hard and fast rule there,
is you can't kill anyone
unless you got a pun.
Shooting someone is out.
Instead it'd be more apropos to like
push someone into the lion's den and say,
he went out for a bite, see?
- Oh, or run someone over
with a steamroller and say,
he was pressed for time.
- Right, like that.
- Or, or how 'bout um,
push a gal out of a plane and then say,
oh she just stepped out.
- Right and then there's
always the classic,
I was all tied up, which means,
- [All] I was all tied up.
(laughing)
- Right.
- You know guys, I just
realized that being a spy
is one of the only times when
a pun is actually acceptable.
- Yeah, ironically, death
actually softens the blow of the pun.
- True.
- You know, I think I'd
like to be a secret agent
just for the pun of it.
(laughs)
- Oh Tom,
I'm gonna rip your
inoperable little arms off
and jettison them into space.
- Oh Crow, you're so disarming.
- D'oh.
Let me at him, let me at him.
- Okay, we'll be right back.
- I really gotta hand it to ya.
- That's it, that-
- You're going out on a limb.
(laughs)
(happy music)
Boy, we're having thumb fun, huh?
- [Crow] Just watch the movie.
- [Joel] Here I'll get my own tip.
- [Crow] The guy's got Snoopy checks.
- [Tom] See what else, here, harmonica?
I just rolled Toots Thielemans.
- [Joel] Oh no, he's
gonna wheelbarrow him.
- [Crow] Now he's a fajita.
- [Tom] Oh boy, huh.
There's an episode of Skinny and Fatty
that's just like this.
- Hey, real comfortable
confessional suite.
Feels good, too.
Hey that was a lucky guess.
(Crow mimics hydraulics)
- [Tom] Oh, come in,
we were just about to float the table.
(chuckles)
- [Crow] (speaks French) Et
monsieur, place your bet.
(tense music)
- [Joel] Hey, he's disguising his throat.
- [Tom] Oh boy, this has all the markings
of a Clay Shaw party.
- [Crow] Whoo!
(Tom humming)
- [Crow] Ladies and
gentlemen, Sandler and Young.
- [Joel] The gentlemen now
retire to the back room
to play Rack-O.
- [Tom] Murray, use a coaster.
- Earth.
Luna.
Pluto.
- [Joel] Goofy, Scrooge McDuck.
- Mars.
Saturn.
Jupiter.
- [Crow] Secret agent
Superdragon in a deadly game of
Hungry, Hungry Hippo.
- [Tom] And uh, this one
I don't think I need to
tell you guys what it is.
- [Man] I'm glad to see you gentlemen.
- [All] Charmed.
- [Joel] The meeting
of the society of guys
who can make a W will now begin.
- [Crow] Watch your fingers guys.
- [Tom] Oh I love it when the table talks,
this is great, watch this, watch, watch.
- The little town of--
- [Tom and Crow] Bethlehem.
- Fremont,
has witnessed the success
of our experiment.
I must impress upon you.
- [Joel] Me?
- The importance of
this success for us all.
- [Tom] Come on boss,
can't the table talk now?
- You will also be glad to
learn the we have liquefied
Synchron 2.
- [Crow] Lickified.
- [Man] This means that
our opportunities of
administering it are limitless.
I'll give you an example.
- [Joel] I'll perform a
puppet show to demonstrate.
- [Crow] Ze booger!
- [Joel] It is the booger.
- [Crow] That is not my booger.
- [Tom] You are looking
directly into room 212.
- [Crow] And now your General
Cinema feature presentation.
- [Joel] Hi.
- [Tom] Hey everybody, look
at the guys in the mirror.
- [Man] And now ladies and gentlemen,
before the piece de
resistance of the evening,
Senor Lamas invites all of
you to drink to the success
of this benefit auction.
- [Crow] And really drink,
down 'em, shooters, whoo!
- [Tom] Petticoat Junction.
- [Joel] Cigars, cigarettes, Tiparillos?
- [Crow] Blonde on blonde on
blonde on blonde on blonde.
- [Tom] It's the Edie Adams gang, ooh.
- In the champagne,
there's a carefully
balanced dose of Synchron 2.
- [Joel] That makes
your hair bouncy, right?
- Just enough of it to amuse us.
In half an hour, they
will remember nothing.
- [Tom] In another half an hour,
they'll be hungry for Chinese.
- [Crow] Oh wow, so this is
what the other half does, hm?
- Thank you, here we go.
- [Joel] It's booze call.
- Here's to those big brown eyes.
- [Tom] Yeah, here's
to your death big guy.
(high-pitched beeping)
- [Crow] Waitress, there's
a squeeze toy in my drink.
- Miss, miss!
I just remembered, I don't drink.
- [Tom] Whoa, close one.
- And now the most precious
treasure of the collection.
The magnificent lute player by Franz Haus.
I ask you ladies and
gentlemen to open the bidding
at one million five
hundred thousand florins.
- [Voiceover] Two million.
- [Tom] Lower.
- Ah two million.
I'm offered two million
once, two million twice and--
- [Voiceover] Three million.
- I'll offer you three and a half.
- [Auctioneer] Anyone
top three and a half?
- Six million.
- [Joel] A bajillion.
- [Crow] A kazillion, jillion,
upteen berdillion.
- That sir, I consider a personal insult.
- [Crow] Hi.
- [Tom] Oh yeah?
- Teach you a lesson.
- [Tom] Oh that sir, I
consider a personal punch.
- [Joel] Oh they've been
given a drink that turns
them into shriners.
- [Crow] Oh how horrible.
- Will you look at that?
- [Tom] Hoohoo!
(Tom laughs)
- [Crow] Hey everybody, let's boink.
- [Tom] It's a good night at Eau Bar.
(people laughing)
- [Crow] Ah, Louis the 14th, good one.
That's two or three mil.
- They're all just behaving like animals.
- [Joel] Hey bring back
the funny pictures.
- What you have seen is
only an example of the
efficiency of Synchron 2.
Whenever we choose to use it,
then victory will be ours.
- [Tom] Victory over what?
- Yes, gentlemen,
the victory will indeed be ours.
- [Crow] Ours the victory will be.
- We are going to change
the course of human life.
The antidote, Anti-Synchron
is known to us and to us alone.
- [Tom] Oh and I told my brother
but he said he wouldn't tell anyone.
- And with it we shall gain world mastery.
Foreign agents have tried to stop us,
notably the invincible Super Dragon.
They have been killed.
The false Ming vases are
now in our possession.
The vases have been sent here
from our factories in India.
- [Joel] We have factories in India?
- The drug is mixed with
a porcelain in such a way
that no one could ever detect it.
- [Crow] But still it's
delicious and low cal.
- In six of them, there is a
sufficient quantity of the drug
to bring to a conclusion
the first phase of the operation.
- [Joel] Phase 1,
swingin' sixties style party.
- [Crow] Whoo!
(crowd laughing)
- [Tom] You're on.
- [Crow] Oh nothing,
nothing. (nervously chuckles)
- [Tom] That's odd,
they're playing Twister where
there ain't no Twister board.
- [Joel] Doris Day, no!
- [Tom] It's Sarina.
- [Crow] I'll fix that, Samantha.
- [Tom] Hello, I am Louis Jordan.
I turn ague,
I walk, I have a gun
and still I am Louis Jordan.
Pardon me while I hit the snack table.
I'm Louis Jordan.
- Don't make a sound, get moving.
- [Joel] Beep.
- Brilliant.
Our compliments.
- [Crow] Mother always calls
during these meetings, sorry.
- I can at last announce to you that
Professor Kruger has been able
to find a-- (audio cuts off)
- [Tom] A what?
- In one hour we will have it.
Gentlemen, await instructions.
- [Joel] Uh, can I ask
why we're at this meeting?
- We will adjourn.
- [Crow] Let's get some of
that kooky champagne, huh?
(moaning)
- [Tom] Ah, crimeny,
Dave's doing his human
cake roll thing again.
You gotta jump on him
and squirt the jelly out.
- [Crow] I'm a naughty
little cheesy blintz.
- [Tom] Cut it out, Dave.
- Get to the embassy right
away, contact Coleman.
The Ming vases are leaving tonight
and must be stopped
and the names and
addresses of all the buyers
investigated, I'll take care of Comfort.
- [Tom] Oh, um, oh I, oh yeah.
(happy music)
- [Tom] Hi, where you
goin'? What are you doin'?
Just wanna walk with you is all.
Nice dress.
- Comfort?
- [Joel] Comfort me.
(woman laughs)
- [Crow] Those guys are
still hopped up on vase.
- [Tom] It was just a case
of mistaken identity, sorry.
- [Joel] Heck of a ride, huh?
Oof!
(soft jazz music)
- [Crow] Well at least
this vicious beating
has a cool accompaniment.
- [Tom] This'll teach you to make blintzes
out of super criminals.
- Now, let's begin with Lamas' number.
- [Crow] Fernando or Lorenzo?
- I'd like to know how you got hold of it.
- But I've told you it was Cooper.
- [All] Oooh!
- The dead don't talk.
- [Joel] You should see this
place around quittin' time.
- You are very beautiful.
- [Crow] She's sure wearing
a funny bathing suit.
- And it would be a pity to
have to put you in our tub.
- [Tom] For you see, the
Mr. Bubble may give you
a urinary infection.
- Tell me have you ever
had a bath in electricity?
- [Crow] Well once I saw
a bear eating a doughnut.
(electronic buzzing)
- [Joel] Hey George Wendt.
- [Tom] Went where?
Ha, another one, thank you.
- [Crow] D'oh, Servo.
- [All] Da-da-da-dum!
- [Tom] This is like The
Quiet Man only it takes place
in a mansion in Holland
with a couple of spies.
Sorry.
- [Crow] Now, now Gary,
this is the last time
you goin' to come home late.
(grunting)
- [Joel] Hey, he's got him in
a secret agent full dragon.
- [Crow] Sisyphus, what's he doing here?
- [Tom] All right.
Time to play the little
blintz game, mister.
- [Woman] Stop.
- You boys stop roughhousing in there.
- Wants him alive.
I thought you were 10 feet under, Bryan.
- [Crow] 10 feet under Bryan?
- Well you were wrong.
- [Joel] Dennis James?
- Like always.
- Not anymore.
Hands up.
- [Tom] Now Simon says put 'em down.
- [Crow] See, she wants me alive, told ya.
You would've gotten into a lot of trouble.
Live?
- [Joel] Oh come to think of it, I did
have a bath like that once, thanks though.
- [Man] This oughta refresh your memory.
- [Crow] And your pores.
- Coward.
- [Tom] Oh all of a sudden
they're at the Alamo.
(thuds)
- [Comfort] You'll pay for this.
We'll get even with you.
- [Crow] Uh, gee, can I have that cell?
(pistol fires)
- [Tom] Oh, right in the cummerbund.
- [Joel] Um, I'm with a client.
Sir, we don't take walk ins.
(pistol fires)
- [Crow] Ooh.
- [Crow] Whoa ho he ho.
- [Tom] It's my groommaid's dress.
- [Crow] Wait, wait, wait, who's alive?
Let's count off here.
(soft jazz music)
- [Joel] Hey it's not my gun,
check the powder burns, I didn't do it.
- [Tom] One last kiss would be nice.
- [Crow] You got a big
ball of wax in there.
- He must tell you.
Everything depends on it.
- It's alright, it's alright now,
don't speak anymore, don't speak anymore.
- [Joel] Alright?
You shot me, you jerk.
- [Crow] I can't believe I ever liked you.
- I couldn't help myself.
- [Crow] I ate the last
(speaking foreign language).
- It was the drug.
- I know.
I always knew.
- [Joel] I knew it was the drug,
you said it was the drug, I knew it.
- [Tom] Know what, it'd
be really bad if you died
while I was kissing you right now.
Now how does that make me feel?
- [Crow] He had to get every
last drop of love out of her.
- [Joel] Well,
I could still hug her,
that's not that weird, is it?
- [Crow] No.
- [Tom] Dead, huh?
Well, heh, best untie the other one.
- [Crow] (sighs) I just let myself out.
- [Tom] The haunting Herb
Alpert death theme here
on the music of your life.
- [Joel] Hey now wait a second,
two wrongs aren't gonna make a right.
- [Crow] Well, I'll do the honors.
Super Dragon worked the
deep fryers at Arby's.
He knows what he's doin.
- [Joel] They're gonna rust proof him.
- [Tom] Now would you guys scrub my back?
Oh, and there's a bottle
of Sardo someplace.
- Well.
- [Joel] Well.
- What have do you have to say to me, huh?
- I got nothing to say.
Just go to hell.
- That's very rude of you.
Comfort?
Teach him some manners.
- [Crow] Well the small
fork is for the shrimp
and keep your head below the queen.
- [Tom] No comfort.
- You won't make me talk.
- All right.
- [Tom] This'll be a shocking experience.
(laughs)
Watts for dinner?
- [Crow] Oh, Servo.
- [Joel] Oh I love it, increase the amps.
Come on.
(electricity buzzing)
- You have a beautiful voice, Salas.
Have you ever thought
about going on the stage?
- You'll both die for this.
- [Crow] Although I was in
Oliver in senior sketch night
and I had this little- (gargling)
- Make her stop it, I'll talk.
- [Joel] Hey it's Frank
the bodyguard's apartment.
- [Tom] What are they in Filene's Basement
all of a sudden?
- [Crow] Jeez, he should put
a fence around that thing,
he might run into problems when
he has a lot of people over,
they could get their head
crushed in or something.
- [Joel] Oh, it's still working anyway.
I haven't been home in a while.
- [Crow] Used to have handles on it.
You could just open it.
It was actually more convenient.
Same deal here, pretty much.
More for show really, I can
get you one if you want one.
- [Joel] Boy, you're really proud of that
clay squirrel, aren't ya?
- I'm very happy to see you again.
- [Tom] I was being facetious.
- Can I give you a hand?
- [Crow] Why sure, you can help us.
(pistol fires)
- [Joel] Just come right in Ray.
- [Tom] He said can I give you a hand.
(laughing)
- He was the only one left
who could tell you the formula
for Anti-Synchron.
- [Crow] Did it have mushroom soup in it?
- Now your mission is failed, Cooper.
Failed totally.
As for me, I couldn't tell
you now, even if I wanted to.
- [Joel] This is my headshot you know?
- [Crow] You hear that Elizabeth?
I'm coming to join you, honey.
- I don't need the formula.
I already photographed it in your office
with this camera, look.
See, huh, huh?
- [Tom] So you're killing
yourself for nothing.
Na, na, na, na, na, na.
- [Joel] What a jerk,
he just wanted to get the guy's goat
right before he died.
- The boys at Fremont are saved
and there's loads of
decorations pouring in for you.
We're just waiting for you to get back.
- [Cooper] Yeah, well
when are you expecting me?
- [Crow] Senator Hawlings,
get off the line.
- Right away of course.
- [Cooper] Well don't hold your breath.
- What?
I don't understand.
- Yeah you heard me all right.
I'm taking a little vacation.
- [Charity] Why?
- Why?
- [Tom] I had the time comin'.
- Holland is beautiful in the fall.
- [Charity] What about Babyface?
- Oh Babyface?
- [Crow] He's beautiful anytime.
- Yeah, I know I gotta send
him right back to Sing Sing,
but I'm afraid I can't do that right now.
He seems to be very, very busy
absorbing the local color.
- [Joel] Appears he's
adopted a Dutch family.
- Now listen, you made a deal with Coleman
to bring him back now.
You can't break your word.
A deal is a deal, do you hear?
Now you and Babyface
get on the first plane--
- [Tom] Flint!
- Well I'm very sorry
but there's nothing I can do about that.
(Tom mimicking sped up voice)
- I'm going to be very busy too.
Studying the local customs.
- [Joel] (chuckles) How about
a little Dutch treat, huh?
- [Crow] At least the
movie had a good payoff.
- Yeah.
(doors closing)
Okay, no, no, no, it's very simple.
- Simple.
- [Joel] Secret.
- Secret simple
- [Joel] Agent.
- Agent thing.
- Super Dragon.
- Secret Super Dragon lady thing.
- Alright, knock it off you mutton heads.
We gotta do that super
villain conference call
with Dr. Forrester.
- Super villain deal, aw forget it.
- Come in, your surliness.
- Sing, sing, sing.
Oh hi Joel.
Dr. Forrester'll be
with you in one minute.
- Ah Mr. Robinson,
why don't you introduce your colleagues?
- Well sirs, pretty
much the same colleagues
as I always have.
Uh, Tom Servo,
Crow T. Robot,
Gypsy couldn't make it.
- [Tom and Crow] Hi.
- Well thank you for coming by today.
Our topic is super villains
and I think I'd like to open it up to
question and answer.
Well thank you, Frank.
- Whatever.
- Can I get some cream?
- No.
- Great, Joel?
- Well I think the question
our field reps ask most
at this week's movie meeting was,
why the super villain in today's film
failed to make any kind of
an impression, gentlemen?
- Right, pretty much,
no impression at all.
- Ah very good.
Well perhaps one reason why
this super villain failed
and I believe the 1971 Dr. No monograph
will back me up here,
is that he did not possess
a strange or rare animal.
I can't be too strong on this point.
Either four legs or two.
Every super villain must have an animal.
Frank, I believe you had a question.
- Oh yeah.
Eagerly,
I've always thought it would
be easy and fun to start up
a super villain franchise, is that true?
- Ah, excellent question, very good.
Uh no, no,
it is
not
easy
to set up a super villain franchise.
You see today's super villain,
is in essence the small
business owner of his franchise.
He does the purchasing,
the hiring, the firing,
plus must maintain medical
and dental and benefits for
an unstable and terribly
dishonest group of henchmen.
But if you are dedicated
and are not afraid of a little hard work,
then you'll find that the
field of super villainry
can be very rewarding indeed.
Yes, next question.
- Well the only thing we wanted to ask
and I think we're all
in agreement on this is-
- [All] What do ya think sirs?
- Good question.
Push the button Frank.
What the, hey.
(epic synthesizer music)
(grunting)